ILGWU Western States Region Records 5780/115
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Novis Denne of Arizona, Incorporated, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Olympiad Sportswear, Incorporated, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Ontario Garment Company, 1973-1976 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Pacific LeBrec Emblem Company, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Paramont Trends, Incorporated, 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Park Pleating Company, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Victor Patino and Nydia Patino, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 27)
- Payson Sportswear, Incorporated, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 28)
- Peggy Lou Corporation, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 29)
- Philip's Draperies of Highland Park, Incorporated, 1978-1979 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Pillowtex, Incorporated, 1977-1978 (Box 29, Folder 31)
- PRC Recording Company [folder 1 of 2], 1984 (Box 29, Folder 32)
- PRC Recording Company [folder 2 of 2], 1984 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- PRC Recording Company: Negotiations, 1976-1978 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- PRC Recording Company, 1978 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Rebuilders Exchange Parts Company, Incorporated, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Rebuilders Exchange Parts Company, Incorporated, 1980-1981 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Fred Rothschild of California, Incorporated, 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Fred Rothschild of California, Incorporated, 1975-1978 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- July Cash Receipts, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- August Cash Receipts, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- September Cash Receipts, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- October Cash Receipts, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- November Cash Receipts, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- December Cash Receipts, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Western States Region: Deposit Slips, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Western States Region: Subordinates Deposit Tickets, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Western States Region: Deposit Tickets, 1973 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Western States Region: Deposit Tickets, 1973-1974 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Western States Region: Deposit Tickets, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Western States Region: Petty Cash, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Western States Region: Petty Cash, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Western States Region: Petty Cash Vouchers, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Account Activity, 1972-1977 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Los Angeles Joint Board: Deposits, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- January to December: Timecards, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Timecards, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Subordinate Accounts, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Subordinate Accounts, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Subordinate Accounts, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Subordinate Accounts, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Administrative Accounts, 1978 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Administrative Accounts, 1976 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Administrative Accounts, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Administrative Accounts, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Administrative Accounts, 1973 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Daily Timecards [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Daily Timecards [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1977 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Western States Region: Administrative Accounts, 1972 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Elections: LA Joint Board Locals, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Local 482, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Local 84: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Local 451: Ballots, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Local 271: Ballots, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Local 55: Elections [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Local 55: Elections [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Local 96: Elections [folder 1 of 2], 1977 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Local 96: Elections [folder 2 of 2], 1977 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- ILGWU Local 270: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- ILGWU Local 278: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- ILGWU Local 512: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- ILGWU Local 97: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- ILGWU Local 184: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- ILGWU Local 277: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- ILGWU Local 294: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- ILGWU Local 385: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- ILGWU Local 430: Elections, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- ILGWU Local Unions, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- ILGWU Election Guidelines, 1976 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  Folder against side of box
- ILGWU: LA Joint Board Minutes, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Nebel, Ben: Correspondence, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Application for Employment and Employee Information File, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Crocker Citizens National Bank, 1973-1978 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Board of Trustees, 1975-1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- ILGWU California Building Corporation: Taxes, 1951-1974 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Union Bank, 1969-1979 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Security Pacific National Bank, 1975-1978 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Cloak Building Corporation: Taxes, 1970-1976 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- State of California: Department of Industrial Relations, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Central States Region, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- County of Los Angeles: Department of Public Social Services, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Certificates of Deposit, 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Central Accounting [folder 1 of 2], 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Central Accounting [folder 2 of 2], 1969-1974 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Bye, Arnold: Director Welfare Benefits Control Department, 1975-1978 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Bernstein, Ted: Counsel [folder 1 of 2], 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Bernstein, Ted: Counsel [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1978 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- ILGWU: Blue Cross Staff and Retirement [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1979 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- ILGWU: Blue Cross Staff and Retirement [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1979 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- Investments: United States Treasury Bills, etc., 1970-1978 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Investments: Western States Region, Subordinates, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 22)
- Feinberg, Basil, 1971-1976 (Box 33, Folder 23)
- Department of Labor: Form EBS-1, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Franchise Tax Board Reports, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- D-2's, 1972-1974 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Wolf and Schulman Accountants, 1970-1978 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Yager, Mitchell, 1974-1979 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Wall, Cornelius: Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Loab, Rhoades and Company (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Teper, Lazare: Director Research Department, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Zalkus, Adolph G: Impartial Chairman, 1962-1969 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- Labor Management Reports, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 33)
- ILGWU Health Services Plan, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Denaro, John: Director Union Label Department, 1971-1978 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Death Benefit Department, 1973-1976 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Chaikin, Sol C: General Secretary-Treasurer, 1975-1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Retiree Service Department, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Wall, Cornelius: V&H, 1972-1976 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- ILGWU San Francisco Joint Board, 1969-1978 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- ILGWU National Retirement Fund, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Lipsig, James: Assistant Executive Secretary, 1973-1976 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Levin, Douglas: Vice President, 1973-1975 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- ILGWU: Supplementary Unemployment Benefits Fund, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Rosenbaum, Irving [folder 1 of 2], 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Rosenbaum, Irving [folder 2 of 2], 1972-1978 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Rolnick, Louis: Administrator, 1975-1978 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Political Reports, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Rules and Regulations of the Los Angeles ILGWU-Employers Fund Health, Vacation and Severance Pay, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Western States Region: Newspaper, 1975-1977 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Jackson, Mattie: San Francisco Joint Board [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Jackson, Mattie: San Francisco Joint Board [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1978 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Political [folder 1 of 2], 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Political [folder 2 of 2], 1974-1978 (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Post Office: Bulk Mailing Information, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Wall, Cornelius: ILGWU, 1971 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- ILGWU: California Votes, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Labor Forum, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Local 497: Election Nomination, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Wolf, Max B., 1969-1973 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  Hebrew
- Younger, Evelle J., 1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Legislation: Los Angeles County, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Legislation: Federal, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Legislation: State, 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Nixon and McGovern, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Alien Employment, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Labor Commissioner: Forms (Box 35, Folder 11)
- United States Department of Labor, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- MDT Advisory Council, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- National Labor Relations Board, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Tariff, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- United States Senate, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Fire Rates, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Food Stamp Program, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Industrial Welfare Commission, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Immigration and Naturalization, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Internal Revenue Service, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Institute of Industrial Relations Association, 1974-1975 (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Immigration: Aliens, Etc., 1970-1972 (Box 35, Folder 23)
- Division of Industrial Welfare [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 24)
- Division of Industrial Welfare [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1976 (Box 35, Folder 25)
- Leonard and Cotrell, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 26)
- Contributions Requests, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Voting Records, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- United States International Trade Commission, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Unemployment and Disability Insurance Committee, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- California Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- California Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board: Forms (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Union Label Department, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Labor Laws, 1978-1980 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Immigration and Naturalization Service: Undocumented Workers, 1975-1978 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Apple Valley Meetings, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Pre-Primary Convention, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Spanish Classes, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- AB 353: Homework, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Legislative Washington Conference, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Legislation: Labor, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Labor Reform, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 17)
- California Labor Federation AFL-CIO: Convention Call, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Education: Discount Programs, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Disability Insurance, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Council on Political Education Convention, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- ILGWU Convention, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Cutters Club: Local 84 and 84M, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Campaign Contributions, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Complaint or Grievance Forms (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Cerrell Associates: News, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Credit Union, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Council on Political Education, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Christmas, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Christmas, 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Complaints, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- 75th Anniversary Diamond Jubilee, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Building Equipment, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Building Projects, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Los Angeles Board of Directors, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Absentees Ballots for Registration, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 19)
- Aid, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- AFL-CIO: Jobs and Trade News, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Alioto Campaign, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Avis Rent A Car System, Incorporated, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Vacation Schedule, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- United Farm Workers, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- U.I.D.I. Determination, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- U.I.D.I. Update, 1966-1974 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Seminar: Triple Header, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- S.T.E.P., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Shop Data, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Social Security, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Spanish Speaking Classes (Box 38, Folder 10)
- California Labor Federation, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Randolph Institute, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Retirement, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Publicity, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Personal, 1973-1975 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Plaza De La Raza, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- Russel, Pat, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- Picnics, 1966 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Political Campaigns: Municipal, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Political Campaigns: State, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- Political Education, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 21)
- ILGWU: Political Department, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 22)
- Pomona County Fair, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 23)
- Postal Service, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 24)
- Optical Department, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 25)
- Organization, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 26)
- Optical Dispensing Office, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 27)
- Optometry Office, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 28)
- O.R.T., 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 29)
- National Prepaid Health Plan, Incorporated, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 30)
- New Members Classes (Box 38, Folder 31)
- Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 32)
- Notary Public Information, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 33)
- The Cloakmaker, 1970-1976 (Box 38, Folder 34)
- Mode O'Day, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 35)
- Memos: Inter-office, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 36)
- Label Department, 1973-1975 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Levy, Van Bourg and Hackler, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 38)
- Labor Law Enforcement: Complaints, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 39)
- Los Angeles County Federation of Labor, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 40)
- Los Angeles Joint Board, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 41)
- Los Angeles-Orange Counties Organizing Committee, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 42)
- Justice, 1973-1975 (Box 38, Folder 43)
- Jewish Labor Committee, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 44)
- Industrial Engineering, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 45)
- Insurance Program, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 46)
- Israel Histadrut, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 47)
- Union Health Center, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 48)
- Health Plans, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 49)
- Histadrut, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 50)
- Department of Human Resources Development, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 51)
- General Executive Board, 1973-1975 (Box 38, Folder 52)
- National Committee to Free Los Tres, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 53)
- Financial Reports, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 54)
- Employee Development Department, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 55)
- ILGWU: Department of Education, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 56)
- Elections: State, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 57)
- Equal Employment Opportunity, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 58)
- Education: Seminars, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 59)
- Education: Classes, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 60)
- Educational Projects, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 61)
- Elections: Los Angeles Joint Board, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 62)
- Engineering, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 63)
- Elections: Southern California District Council, 1973 (Box 38, Folder 64)
- Election Campaign Contributions, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 65)
- ILGWU: Campaign Committee, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 66)
- Elections: State Campaigns, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 67)
- Election Analysis and Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 68)
- Analysis, 1973-1974 (Box 38, Folder 69)
- Elections: Arizona, Utah, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- President Stulberg, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- M.D.T.A., 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Imperial Leather, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- ILGWU: Engineering, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Resolutions, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Meeting Notices, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Education Department, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Union Agreements (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Flu Shots, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Executive Boards, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- The Cloakmaker, 1963-1968 (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Camera, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 14)
- Brewster, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 15)
- Golden Club, 1967-1968 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Christmas, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Winbush, Delois: Arizona, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Mode O'Day, 1968-1972 (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Mode O'Day, 1970-1972 (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Elections: Southern California District Council, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 21)
- Shop Chairladies, 1972 (Box 39, Folder 22)
- Approved Allocations, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 23)
- Bernardino, Sam, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 24)
- Wolf, Max: Organization, 1968-1969 (Box 39, Folder 25)
- Education and Political Committee, 1971-1973 (Box 39, Folder 26)
- Union Documents, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 27)
- Vercher, Tracy, 1971-1972 (Box 39, Folder 28)
- Rubinger, Barbara, 1971 (Box 39, Folder 29)
- Cloak Agreements Hi-Lites, 1970-1973 (Box 39, Folder 30)
- Elections: Joint Board, 1962-1971 (Box 39, Folder 31)
- California Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- California Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- California Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board, 1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- ILGWU: Union Health Center, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- ILGWU: Union Health Center, 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- The Illegal Alien: The Union View (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Labor Commissioner: Division of Labor Standards Enforcement, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Lists Districts and Maps [folder 1 of 2], 1976-1981 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Lists Districts and Maps [folder 2 of 2], 1976-1981 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Los Angeles County Federation of Labor, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Legislative Alert, 1977-1980 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Legislative Correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Domestic Policy, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Department of Fair Employment and Housing, 1977-1980 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Hadassah (Box 41, Folder 10)
- General News Letter, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Hertz, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Histadrut, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 13)
- Imports, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 14)
- Immigration and Naturalization Service, 1975-1981 (Box 41, Folder 15)
- Inside Labor, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Item 807, 1979 (Box 41, Folder 17)
- News Release Employment Development Department, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 18)
- A Social and Economic Profile, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 19)
- Coalition of Labor Union Women, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 20)
- Chinatown, 1975-1979 (Box 41, Folder 21)
- City of Hope, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 22)
- Committee of Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 41, Folder 23)
- Constitutional Rights Foundation, 1981 (Box 41, Folder 24)
- Wolf, Max B: Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 25)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Education, 1974-1981 (Box 41, Folder 26)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Educational [folder 1 of 2], 1975-1980 (Box 41, Folder 27)
- Wolf, Max B: Political and Educational [folder 2 of 2], 1975-1980 (Box 41, Folder 28)
- Wolf, Max B: Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings and Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 41, Folder 29)
- Wolf, Max B: Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings and Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1977-1981 (Box 41, Folder 30)
- Tax Assessment Appeals Board, 1980 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Textile Codes, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Transparent (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1975-1979 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- United Garment Workers, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Unit Pricing, 1977-1979 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Undocumented Workers, 1975-1978 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Unemployment Insurance Precedent Benefit Decision, 1973-1980 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Work Sharing, 1978-1981 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- News Letter, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Western States Region: News Letter, 1975-1981 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  Chinese, Spanish
- Staff Seminar, 1973-1981 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Statement on Immigration (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Staff Seminars: Education Programs, 1973-1977 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Seminar, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Staff Seminar [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1981 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Staff Seminar [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1981 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Staff Seminar, 1976-1981 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Steering and Finance Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Newsletter's Layout, 1979 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Proposition 13, 1978-1979 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Registrar, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Rockefeller Foundation, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Retirement, 1976-1981 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Childcare, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 25)
- California Department of Industrial Relations: Newsletter, 1975-1980 (Box 42, Folder 26)
- Business Agents Reports, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Business Agents Reports, 1978-1981 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- California Labor Federation AFL-CIO, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- California Labor Federation AFL-CIO, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Contract Reviews, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Wall, Cornelius: Outgoing Correspondence, 1979-1981 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Wall, Cornelius: Incoming Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Cost of Living Bulletins, 1977-1979 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Los Angeles Garment Workers: Federal Credit Union, 1974-1978 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Los Angeles Garment Workers: Federal Credit Union, 1970-1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Memorandums, 1972-1979 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Lockiec, Mitchell: Management Engineering Department, 1978-1979 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Contract Reviews, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 14)
- Bay Area ILGWU: Welfare, Health and Vacation Fund, 1966-1979 (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Galin, Lawrence, 1970-1973 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- ILGWU: Los Angeles, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Occupational Testing Program, 1960-1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- ILGWU: California, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- ILGWU: California, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- ALF-CIO Convention, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Executive Board, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Los Angeles Department of City Planning, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- San Francisco, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- ILGWU: Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Environmental Impact Report (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Employment Services Board, 1976-1978 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles City Planning Department, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Wolf, Max: Newspaper Clippings, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- ILGWU: Agreements, 1970-1978 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- ILGWU: California, Los Angeles, 1975-1977 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Employment Development Division, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- ILGWU: California Employment, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- California Unemployment, 1946-1973 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Employment Information, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Plant Closures: Runaway Plants, Volume 1 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Unemployment Insurance, 1974-1980 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Plant Closures, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- California Unemployment Insurance Program Handbook, 1970 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Plant Closures: Runaway Plants, Volume 2 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- The National Commission on Unemployment Compensation, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Employment Development Department, 1975-1980 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- ILGWU: Miscellaneous, 1972-1975 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- ILGWU: Miscellaneous, 1972-1980 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- ILGWU: Miscellaneous, 1979-1980 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- AUDC Local 385: Salt Lake City, 1971-1973 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Southern California District Council, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Local 70: Portland, Oregon, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- AUDC Local 277, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- AUDC Local 430, 1972-1973 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Western States Region: Subordinates Investments, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Per Capita: Arizona, Utah, D.C., California, 1971-1972 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Arizona, Utah: Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- General Schedules, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Western States Region: Local 430, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- SCDC Local 451, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- SCDC Local 497, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- SCDC Local 270, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- SCDC Local 271, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- SCDC Local 293, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Financial Reports, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 16)